Uriel Z. Rivera

2510 Western Avenue #201 Seattle, WA 98121 (619) 909 - 7424 urivera216@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Diligent and adaptive with 5+ years of Customer Service experience, 2 years of Managerial experience, and 3 years of experience in Digital Media & Technology cultivated within various work environments and industries. Has the ability to formulate solutions to real-world problems using an innovative and creative thought process. Consistently looking to gain practical knowledge and experience in the Tech and Design industries while simultaneously prioritizing client satisfaction through positive and favorable interactions.

EXPERIENCE

Torrey Holistics, San Diego, California

Junior Supervisor – JUNE 2020 - JANUARY 2021

Dispatch / Technical Support – FEBRUARY 2020 - JUNE 2020

- Assists upper-management through research to construct creative and fresh ideas for implementation.
- Attends weekly meetings to discuss and develop new promotional events, and materials for the company and vendors.
- Observes, analyzes, and compares exhibited products to existing similar products to help understand market trends and better help the company in planning and implementation.
- Investigated reported issues and walked customers through scripted service protocols.
- Provide technical support to end-users of proprietary software and company websites.
- Answer questions about products and resolve user issues.
- Documented all issues and generated reports detailing the common issues and errors.
- Responded to customer accounts requests, such as billing and account services.

BDK Printwerks, Honolulu, Hawai'i — Freelance Graphic Designer

AUGUST 2017 - DECEMBER 2020

- Designed and implemented Promotional material and Merchandise for upcoming events and promotions.
- Wrote and developed content for the company's website and promotional campaigns (Weekly & Monthly Promotions)
- Revised and updated the company's policies/pricing on an annual basis to keep up with the industry standards and rates.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google IT
 Professional Support
 Certificate
- CompTIA A+

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Technical Support:
 Installing and
 configuring hardware,
 software, and networks
- Computer Networking:
 Standard protocols
 regarding TCP/IP and
 networking services
- Systems Administration:
 Server management,
 User/information
 management
- IT Security: evaluating potential risks and utilizing encryption algorithms and techniques
- Office 365

 Administration:
 deployment,
 troubleshooting, and
 security
- Google Drive Apps:
 Docs, Sheets, & Slides
- Adobe Creative Suite:
 Acrobat, InDesign,
 Illustrator, &
 Photoshop

Developed marketing strategies utilizing situational analysis.

Hickam Skate Hangar, Honolulu, Hawai'i — Manager

APRIL 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

Consistently provided friendly guest service and heartfelt hospitality through in-person interactions

Developed and enforced safety standards and procedures for food quality and sanitation purposes

Maintained established merchandising standards, including window, sales floor and promotional displays.

Used complex membership system (VerifyPro) to organize and add new memberships to roster, as well as making reservations for member parties and rentals

Keyholder; responsible for opening, closing, sanitation and security of park

EDUCATION

San Diego City College, San Diego, California — Associates of Applied Arts, Digital Media / Graphic Design

JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2020

University of Hawaii, Honolulu, Hawai'i — Graphic Design

AUGUST 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

• Digital Media / Graphic Design (Transferred)

Moanalua High School, Honolulu, Hawai'i — *High School Diploma*

AUGUST 2013- MAY 2017

REFERENCES

Michael Kays, BDK Skate Design LLC — Founder

(808) 230-7614

Daisy Rivera, Aerospace — Executive Assistant

(323) 401-2000

Chela Sheets, Moanalua High School/Herff Jones Yearbook
—Associate Rep (Hawai'i) / Photography & Yearbook
Instructor

(808) 398-0921

• Typing: 85 WPM avg.

SKILLS

- Customer-Oriented
- Detail-Oriented
- Active Listening Skills
- Highly Organized
- Independent & Team Oriented
- Analytical & Creative Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

English (Native)

Spanish (Conversationally)